<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Diabetes2</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_activity_profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="title_activity_info">Info</string>
    <string name="info"><![CDATA[<h2><font color="#96d3ea">Type 2 diabetes</font></h2><p>Type 2 diabetes is a chronic condition that occurs when the pancreas does not produce enough insulin and / or the insulin does not work effectively to meet the body needs.</p><p>Type 2 diabetes:</p><br>Represents 85 to 90 of all cases of diabetes<br><br>Is more likely in people with a family history of type 2 diabetes or from particular ethnic backgrounds<br><br>Usually develops in adults over the age of 45 years but is increasingly occurring in younger age groups<br><br>Can be delayed or prevented in 58 of cases<br><font color="#96d3ea">Symptoms of Type 2 diabetes</font> </h2><p> Symptoms may include <b>blurred vision, skin infections, slow healing, tingling and numbness in the feet.</b> Sometimes no symptoms are noticed at all.</p>]]></string>
    <string name="title_activity_diabetes2_found">Diabetes2Found</string>
    <string name="ManageDiabetes"><![CDATA[<h2>Manage Diabetes Now page Content </h2><br><br><p>Managing Diabetes type 2 <p><br></br><p>Congratulations – you’ve taken the first step in learning more about managing your diabetes and living your life.</p><br><br><p>Diabetes Advisor is here to help you on your journey. Learning about healthy food choices, the importance of physical activity, the health care team, blood glucose monitoring and preventing complications can help you to live well with type 2 diabetes.</p>]]></string>
    <string name="EatHealthy"><![CDATA[<p><b>Healthy eating<b> is an important part of managing type 2 diabetes. This means paying close attention to what, when, and how much you eat on a daily basis.</p>]]></string>
    <string name="Physicalactivity"><![CDATA[<h2>Physical activity Page: </h2><br><p>Physical activity is vital in maintaining a healthy lifestyle. By becoming more active you can improve your general health, quality of life and diabetes management.</p><p>Participating in regular physical activity helps to:</p><p>•	Improve insulin sensitivity (makes insulin work better and lowers blood glucose levels)</p><br><p>•	Improve blood pressure and lowers blood fats, which reduces the risk of heart disease</p><br><p>•	Achieve and maintain a healthy body weight</p><br><p>•	Increase bone strength and reduce the risk of osteoporosis</p><br><p>•	Improve quality of life and sense of well being</p><br><p>•	Slow down the ageing process</p><br><p>For the person with diabetes, physical activity helps to </p><br><p>•	Improve the body’s response to insulin which can lower blood glucose level</p><br><p>•	Lower blood pressure and cholesterol levels</p><br><p>•	Reduce the risk of developing diabetes complications</p><br><h4>Activities:</h4><p>Aerobic activities that get your muscles moving such as walking, swimming or cycling are recommended.</p><br><p>Strength training activities that make you use your muscles such as squats, lifting weight are recommended.</p><br><p>For daily activity plan contact us on (provide email id).</p>]]></string>
    <string name="stories"><![CDATA[<p>My name is Kate and I’m just an ordinary person leading an ordinary life. What makes me somewhat different, is that I am living my ordinary life with Type 2 diabetes.</p><p>I’d like to say that makes me unique, but the sad truth is that every day, more and more people are being diagnosed with this disease. Even worse, there are thousands upon thousands of people who don’t even know they are already affected.</p><p>OK, so I have diabetes. Now what? When I saw the doctor, she said I needed to exercise and change my diet. Losing some weight would be beneficial. She told me to get a glucose meter to check my blood glucose at various times during the day: first thing in the morning, before a meal, two hours after a meal, at bedtime, when the moon is full, on trash day…What? What did she say?</p><p>Be mindful of what you’re eating and how much of each thing: no more than so many grams of fat, so much protein and about 30 grams of carbs per meal</p><p>I left that doctor’s office in a daze. I knew that I had to make some changes, but I wasn’t sure where to begin. I’m intelligent. I can figure this out! I just had to deal with it. This App helped me a lot learning about the life style that diabetes type 2 people have to maintain. To overcome it.</p>]]></string>
    <string name="title_activity_diabetes_sub_menu">diabetes_sub_menu</string>
    <string name="title_activity_eat_healthy">EatHealthy</string>
    <string name="title_activity_physicalactivity">Physicalactivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_eat_healthy_link">EatHealthyLink</string>
    <string name="title_activity_stories">stories</string>

</resources>
